Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Jack Peters Papers, 1965-1989 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Client Files, 1965-1987 and undated, (38 boxes)
  - Ford (U.S.A.)
    - Compensation, 1986 (Box 26)
    - Composite Situation, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Contemporary Markets Program Proposal, 1982 (Box 26)
    - Corporate files, 1979-1986 (Box 26)
    - Current Escort files, 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Dealer files, 1983-1986 (Box 27)
    - Detroit: Myth vs. Reality presentation, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Escort Marketing Manual (Box 27)
    - Event marketing, 1986 Ford Taurus, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Face of Ford presentation, 1980 (Box 27)
    - FasPac presentation, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Final speech, 1979 July 25, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Financial, 1978-1985, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Financial and Purchasing Status Report, 1979 (Box 28)
    - Ford Corporate Reputation Campaign, 1983 (Box 28)
    - Ford Dealer Association
      - Chairman's meetings, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 28)
      - Meeting, general, 1987 (Box 28)
      - Newark presentation, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Ford Division
      - Chairman's meeting, 1985 July 23-25 (Box 28)
      - New Car Show, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Ford, Edsell
      - General files, 1981-1984 (Box 28)
      - Meeting, 1981 (Box 28)
    - Ford Network Senior Management meetings, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Ford Performance Group, 1983 (Box 28)
    - Ford Project, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Ford U.S. Project Advantage, 1982 (Box 28)
    - Bob Graham presentation, 1981 May 20 (Box 28)
    - Handbook of Procedures and Checklist of Items Useful in Launching a New Automotive Product, circa 1983 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Walter Hayes files
      - Presentation, 1980 Feb. (Box 28)
      - Project, 1980 (Box 28)
    - Iacocca presentation, 1978 May 3 (Box 29)
    - If You Really Listened campaign, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Interview, 1980 Aug. 13 (Box 29)
    - Don Johnston files
      - General files, 1978-1983, (3 folders) (Box 29)
      - Ad Age Caldwell letter, 1980 (Box 29)
    - JWT Board of Directors presentation, 1978 (Box 29)
    - JWT Detroit Purchasing Manual, 1983 (Box 29)
    - JWT Ford situation, 1978-1979 (Box 30)
    - JWT performance evaluations, 1979-1987, (2 folders) (Box 30)
    - K&E Chrysler situation, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Marilyn King material, 1980-1981 (Box 30)
    - Launching Erika to the Press, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Legal files, 1983-1986 (Box 30)
    - Lutz presentation, 1982 (Box 30)
    - MacKenzie PR project, 1978-1980 (Box 30)
    - Management presentation, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Jack McDougall files
      - Meeting, 1980 (Box 30)
      - Presentations, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Media
      - General files, 1982-1986 (Box 31)
      - Meeting with Television Network Executives, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Meetings, 1983, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - More Better Ideas at Ford, 1972 (Box 31)
    - Motor Trend Car of the Year Ford meeting, 1986 (Box 31)
    - NAAO
      - Campaign, Review of Media Issues, 1982 (Box 31)
      - Meeting, 1982 Sept. 28 (Box 31)
      - Presentation biographies, 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 31)
      - Product Support Campaign, 1982 (Box 31)
      - Project, 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 31)
      - Quality Program, Addendum to Letter of Terms, 1982 (Box 31)
      - Quality Campaign Push with Y&R, 1981-1982 (Box 31)
      - Quality Program
        - Quality is Job # 1 Strategy, 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 31)
        - Staffing and compensation, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Naming, 1966-1970 (Box 32)
    - Network information, 1984-1987 (Box 32)
    - Old Ford U.S. material, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
    - Organizational structure, circa 1980 (Box 32)
    - Personnel, 1978 (Box 32)
    - Peterson-Lutz presentation, 1983 Jan. 20, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Peterson meetings
      - Meeting files, 1980-1983, (2 folders) (Box 32)
      - Presentation, 1980 Sept. (Box 32)
    - Planning, 1981-1985 (Box 33)
    - Policies and procedures, 1983-1985 (Box 33)
    - Policy Agency Changes, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Policy Agency Changes Agreement, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Harold Poling files
      - Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 33)
      - Poling-Benton visit, 1981 May 4 (Box 33)
      - Poling visit, 1982 July 28 (Box 33)
    - Presentations, 1965, 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Presentation boards, 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Production Accounting and Cost Control Procedures, undated (Box 33)
    - Publicity, 1978-1983 (Box 33)
    - Public relations, 1978-1985 (Box 34)
    - Public relations, publicity program, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Racing, 1978-1983 (Box 34)
    - Ranger-Escort meeting, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Refocusing the Spotlight, North American Automotive Operations, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Regional marketing presentation, 1983 Aug. 11 (Box 34)
    - Retention Reports, 1979-1981, (3 folders) (Box 34)
    - Retest of television commercial, Rolls Royce, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Review, 1978 Nov. (Box 34)
    - Rolls Royce marketing, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Roper Report, Way Out West, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Special Ford/FDAF/JWT analysis, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Jackie Stewart files
      - Jackie Stewart NAAO Campaign, 1982 July 29 (Box 34)
      - Jackie Stewart Product Support Campaign, 1982-1984, (2 folders) (Box 35)
      - Jackie Stewart's Role in Ford Advertising, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Strategy Review, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Taurus Launch Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 35)
    - Thunderbird, 1979, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Traverse City FDAF/RMP field meetings, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Traverse City FDAF presentation, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Trip files, 1985-1986, (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Trucks, 1980-1986 (Box 35)
    - John Vanderzee meeting, 1986 Mar. 6 (Box 36)
    - Walla presentation, 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Warranty, 1983 (Box 36)
    - What a Time It Is for Ford, 1979 (Box 36)
    - What the Press Says about Escort and Lynx Technology, 1980 (Box 36)
    - World Car Position for Erika, 1979 (Box 36)
    - World Car II, 1980 (Box 36)
    - Y&R situation, 1979 (Box 36)
  - Ford (Worldwide)
    - General files, 1982-1985, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Managers meeting, 1984 (Box 36)
    - Clark Vitulli's Direct Marketing Day speech, 1985 (Box 36)
    - [boxes not used] (Box 37, 38)
  - Ford Personnel Files [RESTRICTED] (Box 39)
    Includes files relating to individual personnel of Ford offices, performance evaluations of office managers, as well as salary information.
    Restriction on Access: Files relating to personnel records are closed for 25 years from the date of the individual employee's death, or 40 years from the date of termination if the date of death cannot be determined.
    - Ford, International, 1979-1986, (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Ford, Toronto, general personnel information, 1979-1981 (Box 39)
    - Ford U.S.A.
      - General personnel files, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 39)
      - Detroit, 1978-1986 (Box 39)
      - Leighton Hardey, 1984 (Box 39)
      - Richard Hayes, 1979-1981, (2 folders) (Box 39)
      - Walter Hayes, 1980 (Box 39)
      - John McDougall, 1980-1981 (Box 39)
      - Personnel request, 1981 (Box 39)
      - Don Petersen, 1980-1985 (Box 39)
      - Red Poling, 1980-1983 (Box 39)
      - Merrill Snyder, 1981-1983 (Box 39)
  - Gerber, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Goodyear (International)
    - General files, 1983-1985 (Box 40)
    - Status of the Goodyear Account, 1983 (Box 40)
    - (Box 40)
  - Goodyear (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Company overview, 1971 (Box 40)
    - International Action Plan, 1984 (Box 40)
    - Pitch, Hit and Throw competition, 1971 (Box 40)
    - Presentation materials, 1969-1981 (Box 40)
    - Presentation, Road Ahead, 1971 (Box 40)
    - Status report, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Guinness (London), 1982 (Box 40)
  - Hallmark, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Hawaiian Express, 1983-1986 (Box 40)
  - Health & Tennis Corporation
    - General files, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
    - Honolulu meeting, 1985 (Box 40)
    - Marketing Plan, 1984 (Box 41)
    - Meeting file, 1985-1986 (Box 41)
  - Herz, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Hewlett-Packard, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Hiram Walker, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Hyatt Hotels, 1986 (Box 41)
  - IBM
    - General files, 1986-1973, (3 folders) (Box 41)
  - International Computers Ltd., 1984 (Box 41)
  - International Wool Secretariat, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Jacobs, 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - Johnson & Johnson, presentation, 1985 (Box 41)
  - K-Mart, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Kellogg's (International)
    - General files, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Denis Lanigan file, 1985 (Box 41)
    - Situation Analysis, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Kellogg's (U.S.A.) (Box 42)
    - General files, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
    - Company Compensation Study, 1985 (Box 42)
    - Worldwide Business Building Plan, 1985 (Box 42)
  - Kodak (International), general files, 1983-1986 (Box 42)
  - Kodak (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Comparison advertising, 1975-1986 (Box 42)
    - Corporate representation, 1975 (Box 42)
    - International Coordination, 1976 and undated (Box 42)
    - Don Johnston file, 1976-1978 (Box 42)
    - Planning process presentation, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Trip file, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - Kraft (International) (Box 43)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 43)
    - Effective Kraft Advertising presentation, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
  - Kraft (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Cheese project, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Kraft-Country Music Awards Show, 1984-1986, (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Trip file, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Worldwide Kraft Account Managers Conference, 1986 (Box 43)
  - [Ligget & Myers Incorporated, Lark Advertising, Annual Plan, 1969, removed to Oversize series.) (Box 43)
  - Löwenbräu, briefing, 1985 (Box 43)
  - Mattel (International), general files, 1983-1986 (Box 43)
  - McConnell-Douglas, general files, 1985 (Box 43)
  - Mexicana Airlines, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Miles, 1981 (Box 43)
  - Miller (International), general files, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Miller (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1978, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Advertising Review, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Agency of Record (AOR) pitch, 1985-1986 (Box 44)
    - Letter of terms, 1986 (Box 44)
    - National sales meetings, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Trip file, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Values and Lifestyle Data, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Nabisco (International), 1986 (Box 45)
  - Nabisco (U.S.A.), 1984-1986 (Box 45)
  - Nestle (International), 1983-1986 (Box 45)
  - Nestle (U.S.A.), 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Northern Telecom, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Orkin, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Oscar Mayer
    - General files, 1985 (Box 45)
    - 25th Anniversary Party, 1985 (Box 45)
  - Paramount, information, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Pepsico (International), general files, 1983-1985 (Box 45)
  - Pepsico, general files, 1984-1986 (Box 45)
  - Philip Morris, general files, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Philips Petroleum (International), general files, 1985 (Box 45)
  - Phonemate, 1985 (Box 45)
  - Playtex (International), Almay division, 1985 (Box 45)
  - Proctor & Gamble, general files, 1986 (Box 45)
  - (Box 46)
  - Quaker
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 46)
    - Bank investigation, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Reader's Digest, 1984 (Box 46)
  - Reynolds Metals
    - General files, 1986 (Box 46)
    - New products, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Reynolds Wrap update, undated (Box 46)
  - Richardson Vicks (London), 1983-1985 (Box 46)
  - R.J. Reynolds (International)
    - General files, 1983-1986 (Box 46)
    - Winston Salem meeting, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Rolex (International), general files, 1981-1982 (Box 46)
  - Rountree (International), general files, 1982-1986 (Box 46)
  - Rountree (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 46)
    - Nestle conflict, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Rountree Mackintosh presentation, 1983 (Box 46)
  - R.T. French, 1984-1986 (Box 46)
  - Rustenburg Platinum, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Ryder, presentation, undated (Box 46)
  - Sasson, 1984 (Box 46)
  - S.C. Johnson (International
    - General files, 1983-1985 (Box 46)
    - JWT International Business Overview, 1983 (Box 46)
    - JWT International Overview, 1983 (Box 46)
  - S.C. Johnson (U.S.A.), general files, 1984-1986 (Box 47)
  - Scott Paper Company, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Sears
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 47)
    - Chicago Office Sears situation, 1983 (Box 47)
    - Sears/Dean Witter, 1983-1984 (Box 47)
  - Showtime, general files, 1984-1985 (Box 47)
  - Six Flags, general files, 1984 (Box 47)
  - Sprint
    - General files, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - AT&T Challenge, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Brief, 1986 (Box 47)
  - Tenneco, general files, 1980-1986 (Box 47)
  - Twentieth Century Fox
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 47)
    - Meeting file, 1984-1985 (Box 48)
    - Rhinestone benefit, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Uncle Ben's, general files, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Unilever (International)
    - General files, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Ad Conference, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Lever Lunch, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Puerto Rico, Latin American presentation, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Unilever-SC Johnson meeting, 1986 (Box 48)
  - Unilever (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 48)
    - Lever Brothers problem, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
  - United Parcel Service
    - Overnight presentation, 1984 (Box 48)
    - Small Package Express Explosion, 1983 (Box 48)
  - U.S. Air
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 48)
    - Target Plan, 1984 (Box 48)
  - U.S. Marine Corps (USMC) (Box 49)
    - General files, 1984-1987, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Awareness and Attitude Tracking Study, 1983 (Box 49)
    - Coldstream Conference, 1984 (Box 49)
    - General Kelley file, undated (Box 49)
  - Warner Lambert (International), general files, 1984-1986 (Box 49)
  - Warner Lambert (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 49)
    - Annual Review, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Briefing, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Presentation, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Trip file, 1986 (Box 49)
  - W.A. Taylor & Co.
    - General files, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Brand Review, 1984 (Box 49)
- Correspondence and Memoranda, 1970-1987 and undated, (8 boxes)
  Contains correspondence primarily between Jack Peters and various JWT employees, as well as general JWT office memoranda. Some items pertain to the 1984-1985 case before the Securities Exchange Commission. Much of the correspondence arrived grouped in Chronological Books ordered by date; these groupings were maintained.
  - General files, 1980-1984 (Box 50)
  - Atlanta Office, 1984-1986 (Box 50)
  - Better Business Bureau, 1986 (Box 50)
  - Chicago Office, 1985-1987 (Box 50)
  - Chronological Books
    - 1983, (4 folders) (Box 50)
    - 1983-1984, (7 folders) (Box 51)
    - 1984, (6 folders) (Box 52)
    - 1984-1985, (8 folders) (Box 53)
    - 1985-1986, (7 folders) (Box 54)
    - 1986, (6 folders) (Box 55)
    - 1986, (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - Combined memos, 1983 (Box 56)
  - Companywide mailing, 1985 (Box 56)
  - Current action, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
  - Dallas Office, 1984 (Box 56)
  - Department of Labor, 1985 (Box 56)
  - Detroit, 1978-1986 (Box 56)
  - Financial
    - General files, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 57)
    - Atlanta, 1984, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Chicago, 1984-1987 (Box 57)
    - Detroit, 1985-1986 (Box 57)
    - Los Angeles, 1984-1986 (Box 57)
    - New York, 1984-1986 (Box 57)
    - Planning, 1985 (Box 57)
    - San Francisco, 1983-1984 (Box 57)
    - Washington, D.C., 1984 (Box 57)
  - Don Johnston files
    - European trip follow-up file, 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Information, 1970-1983 (Box 57)
  - Legal files, 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Los Angeles, 1984-1987 (Box 57)
  - Mailings to offices, undated (Box 57)
  - Memos from Chairman, 1983-1984 (Box 57)
  - Memos from President, 1985 (Box 57)
  - Bert Metter, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Minority Media, 1984-1986 (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 57)
  - New York Office, 1984-1987 (Box 57)
  - Joe O'Donnell, 1986 (Box 57)
  - San Francisco, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Security Exchange Commission Investigation, 1984-1985 (Box 57)
- International Offices, 1979-1988 and undated, (9 boxes)
  Contains correspondence, meeting reports, travel documentation, presentation files, audit information, information on features of various markets in specific regions, as well as general administrative memoranda for JWT's international offices. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically by region, country or city, depending on the original designation.
  - General, three year plans, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
  - Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
  - Amsterdam, 1982-1986 (Box 58)
  - Argentina, 1980-1986 (Box 58)
  - Asia Pacific
    - General files, 1983-1986, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Operational Review, 1986 (Box 58)
  - Australia
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
    - Executive Report Summary, 1986 (Box 58)
    - Melbourne
      - Introduction, undated (Box 58)
      - Presentation to Jack Peters, 1986 (Box 58)
    - Operational Summary for 1986 (Box 58)
    - Sydney, presentation to Jack Peters, 1986 (Box 58)
    - Trip, 1986 (Box 58)
  - Brazil, 1983-1986 (Box 59)
  - Brussels
    - General files, 1980-1986 (Box 59)
    - Situation, 1986 (Box 59)
  - Canada
    - General files, 1986 (Box 59)
    - JWT Canada Regional Reviews, 1986 (Box 59)
    - Operating Policies Manual, 1984 (Box 59)
    - Toronto office space recommendations, 1985 (Box 59)
  - Caracas
    - General files, 1981-1986 (Box 59)
    - Regional Management Review, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Central Pacific, 1986 (Box 59)
  - Chile
    - General files, 1980-1984 (Box 59)
    - Presentation: Some Dos and Don'ts Based on What We Have Learnt in Chile, 1982 (Box 59)
  - China (Box 60)
    - General files, 1986 (Box 60)
    - Profile, 1985 (Box 60)
    - Review of Ad Market, 1985 (Box 60)
  - Columbia, 1981-1985 (Box 60)
  - Denmark, 1980-1986 (Box 60)
  - Dubai
    - General files, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Accounts receivable, 1985 (Box 60)
    - Press, 1985-1986 (Box 60)
    - Reports, 1985 (Box 60)
  - Ecuador
    - General files, 1980-1983 (Box 60)
    - Latin American Managers Meeting, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Egypt, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Europe, 1985-1986 (Box 60)
  - France (Box 61)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 61)
    - Paris, Acquisition Project, 1983 (Box 61)
  - Germany, 1979-1986, (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Greece
    - General files, 1982-1986 (Box 61)
    - JWT Italy Retained Dividends in Greece, 1985 (Box 61)
    - Spot Thompson, 1980-1985 (Box 61)
  - Guatemala, 1985 (Box 61)
  - Hong Kong
    - General files, 1981-1986 (Box 61)
    - Internal Audit Report, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Indonesia, 1981-1986 (Box 61)
  - India, 1982-1986 (Box 61)
  - JWT Worldwide, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Korea, 1983-1986 (Box 62)
  - Kuala Lumpur
    - General files, 1981-1986 (Box 62)
    - Denis Lanigan visit, 1984 (Box 62)
  - Latin America, 1983-1986 (Box 62)
  - London
    - General files, 1980-1986 (Box 62)
    - Frank Small and Associates, 1984-1985 (Box 62)
    - Lexington International, 1981-1982 (Box 62)
    - MRBI
      - General files, 1982-1983 (Box 62)
      - MRBI, 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Meeting, 1983 Mar. 30 (Box 63)
      - Promotional, undated (Box 63)
    - Pension Scheme, 1984 (Box 63)
    - Revised Marketing Plan, 1986-1988 (Box 63)
  - Malaysia Agreement, 1987 (Box 63)
  - Manchester, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
  - Mexico City, 1984-1987 (Box 63)
  - Middle East
    - General files, 1982-1986, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Arab Agency Profile, 1982 (Box 63)
    - MERAC, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Middle East Report, 1981 (Box 64)
    - Middle East Saga Report, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Report on meeting with Erwin Guerrovich of Intermarkets, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Taj Group profile, 1982 (Box 64)
  - Milan
    - General, 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 64)
    - Sam Meek seminar, 1984 (Box 64)
  - New Zealand, 1984-1986 (Box 64)
  - Nigeria, 1981-1983 (Box 64)
  - Norway and Finland, 1985-1986 (Box 64)
  - Pakistan, 1982-1983 (Box 64)
  - Paraguay, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Philippines
    - General files, 1981-1986 (Box 64)
    - Manila speech, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Portugal, 1982-1986 (Box 64)
  - Singapore, 1981-1987 (Box 65)
  - South Africa
    - General files, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Johannesburg, 1982-1986 (Box 65)
    - Marketing plan, 1985-1987 (Box 65)
  - Spain
    - Barcelona, 1982-1985 (Box 65)
    - Madrid
      - General files, 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Sri Lanka, 1980-1985 (Box 65)
  - Sweden
    - Ronnberg, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Stockholm, 1981-1982 (Box 65)
  - Taiwan, 1985-1986 (Box 65)
  - Thailand, 1982-1986 (Box 65)
  - Tokyo
    - General files, 1981-1982 (Box 65)
    - General files, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - Executive Report Summary, 1986 (Box 66)
    - JMRB Review, 1983 (Box 66)
    - Thompson Real Estate Japan, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Turkey
    - General files, 1984-1985, (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - Documents from Turkey, 1982 (Box 66)
    - Visit to Turkey, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Uruguay, 1985 (Box 66)
  - Vienna
    - General files, 1981-1986 (Box 66)
    - JWT Vienna and the Austrian Market, 1984 (Box 66)
  - Zurich, 1981-1985 (Box 66)
- Meetings, 1980-1989 and undated, (7 boxes)
  Contains charts, presentation scripts, memoranda and logistical information, and notes pertaining to various JWT meetings and general advertising events. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically by meeting title. Board of Directors and Managers meetings were arranged chronologically.
  - Acetates for financial meetings, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Advertising Management Group, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - American Advertising Federation Board Meetings, 1980-1989 (Box 67)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 67)
  - Analysts meetings, 1982-1985 (Box 67)
  - Annual meetings, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Art Committee meetings, 1985, (3 folders) (Box 67)
  - Atlanta, Curtis Mathes meeting file, 1985 (Box 67)
  - Board of Directors meetings
    - 1980 Sept. 18 (Box 67)
    - 1980 Dec. 17 (Box 67)
    - 1981 Mar. 24 (Box 67)
    - 1981 June 9, (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - 1984 Jan. 31, (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - 1984 June 6 (Box 68)
    - 1984 Aug. (Box 68)
    - 1984 Oct. (Box 68)
    - 1984 Nov. 28 (Box 68)
    - 1985-1987 general (Box 68)
    - 1985 Mar. 7 (Box 68)
    - 1985 May 9 (Box 68)
    - 1985 June 19 (Box 68)
    - 1985 Sept. 12-13 (Box 69)
    - 1985 Nov. 12 (Box 69)
    - 1985 Dec. 3 (Box 69)
    - 1986, general (Box 69)
    - 1986 Mar. 4 (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - 1986 Mar. 10 (Box 69)
    - 1986 May 8 (Box 69)
    - 1986 Aug. 26 (Box 69)
    - 1986 Sept. 11 (Box 69)
    - 1986 Oct. 22, (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - 1986 Dec. 2 (Box 69)
  - Board of Directors, Proposal for Progress from the Strategy Committee, 1980 (Box 69)
  - Chicago Office building meeting, 1986 Dec. 4 (Box 69)
  - Current JWT Board file, 1986, (3 folders) (Box 69)
  - Current JWT meeting file, 1986 (Box 70)
  - Dinner meeting, 1987 Nov. 25 (Box 70)
  - Executive Committee, 1986 Apr. 30 (Box 70)
  - Financial meetings, New York, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - General conference information, 1986 (Box 70)
  - General managers, 1986 Feb. 11 (Box 70)
  - Golden West/Chevron Broadcasters Palm Springs Weekend, 1984, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Group Review, 1987 Jan. 13 (Box 70)
  - Don Johnston meeting files
    - Meeting, 1986 (Box 70)
    - Presentation, 1986 Dec. 10 (Box 70)
  - JWT Company Fund meetings
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 70)
    - Agendas
      - 1984 Feb. 13 (Box 70)
      - 1986 June 11 (Box 70)
  - JWT Group (Box 71)
    - Board meeting, 1986 Dec. 2, (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - Board presentation, 1984 Apr. 3 (Box 71)
  - Managers meetings
    - 1980 May 1, New York (Box 71)
    - 1980 June, Detroit (Box 71)
    - 1982 Nov., Atlanta (Box 71)
    - 1983 Apr. 8-9, San Francisco (Box 71)
    - 1984-1986, general files (Box 71)
    - 1984 Feb. 1, New York (Box 71)